♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 18=
Governor, something's wrong.
Special Ops reported
the Xiaosheng Society's men
have taken Mr. Rong.
(Xiaosheng Society took Rong Xiaonan,
Special Ops)
I didn't kill him.
You'an, you wouldn't kill me.
Governor.
We can move now.
Yes.
Governor.
Are the troops all assembled?
The city garrison
received orders early this morning
and were redeployed.
They said it was your handwritten order.
Now the communication lines are down.
We can't get through.
One more thing.
Backyard guards reported...
Xu Fan is missing, right?
He must have had someone
help him escape over the wall.
And, about the forged handwritten order,
I've had it looked into.
No need for that.
What a clever scheme.
I was too soft-hearted
towards that cunning one.
What about the Xiaosheng Society?
The Special Ops reports
they've recently hired
a large number of thugs
and are heavily guarded.
Order the Xishan battalion
troops into the city.
You go personally.
When you're there, signal with a shot.
We'll strike from both sides.
Yes.
I know you're worried about him.
I won't abandon him.
He's not the only one I'm worried about.
Take me with you.
I don't want to lose anyone important.
Not a single one.
Alright. Come with me.
Come on.
Where are we?
Aren't we going
to the Xiaosheng Society?
Before we go, there's something
I need to ask of you.
In those war-torn years,
my mother and I wandered everywhere.
We always thought if we outran the war,
we could survive.
I never expected
that in the end, she died in the war
because of a bag of millet.
I've always wanted
to put up a memorial grave for her.
After thinking it over,
I finally thought of this place.
When it's Qingming,
please tend to the place
and pay respects for me.
The ceremony wasn't completed,
but
we're still family.
If so, we should come
and pay respects together.
Don't say such unlucky things.
Let's make this place
our home from now on.
I didn't expect it to still be here.
How can it be?
Isn't this Mr. Rong's token?
Why is it here?
What did you say?
This is Rong Xiaonan's thing?
Yes.
It's the token between him
and his brother.
He once asked me to find
the person with the same token.
But I searched all over Fengcheng
and never found that person.
Zhuzi.
I once had a brother.
And we only had each other.
I've searched for years
and never found a trace of him.
Stop!
Over here!
Run!
Brother!
Take him to the barracks!
Move!
Brother!
Did he tell you
anything about someone named Shitou?
He...
Before going undercover
to assassinate, he thought he'd die.
So he left me a farewell letter.
He asked me
to make sure I find his brother
and see if he's still alive.
Y-You are Mr. Rong's brother?
Let's go rescue him together.
We three will come back together.
Alright.
But the Xiaosheng Society
is not what it used to be.
To rescue Zhuzi,
you need to mobilize a troop for me.
I'll go and scout the layout first.
Alright.
Don't worry.
I've arranged everything.
They will follow your orders.
See you at the Xiaosheng Society's gate.
Alright.
What's going on?
Sorry, Madam.
These are the Governor's orders.
He told me to drive
until we run out of petrol,
as far as possible.
What do they take me for?
Someone who's only there for the good?
Open the door!
Madam, stop running.
We're already out of the city.
You will not run back tonight.
(You really are brothers,)
(telling the same lie
at the worst possible moment.)
No.
I must go back.
I know you're all tough.
Today, I'll let you taste
the power of my foreign drug.
It can amplify nerve pain
a hundred times.
Rest assured,
I've tested it
on those women in Fengcheng.
Their screams were piercing
and pleasant.
The effect was remarkable.
You'll die a horrible death!
I heard you sing opera well.
This drug can damage your nerves.
I'm afraid you'll never be able
to sing opera again.
Is that all you've got?
You're useless.
Coward!
Boss.
That scoundrel Xu Fan was right.
Xu You'an indeed recklessly
rushed over to save you.
Where is Rong Xiaonan?
You didn't really think
Xu Fan had gone crazy, did you?
You know what?
He's not crazy
and wants to hit two birds
with one stone,
so we both win.
Take a guess.
Will the brave and resourceful Xu You'an
be able to walk
out of this door alive today?
That scoundrel Xu Fan
was faking his madness?
Let me go! I will kill him
with my own hands!
I'll kill him!
I'll see him ruined
beyond all recovery!
Tell Du Xiaolin to bring him out!
Buddies! Hack him to death!
(Xiaosheng Society)
What exactly do you want?
The Jade Buddha Head?
But why involve Xu You'an?
It's true that I want the Buddha Head.
But Xu Fan wants Xu You'an's life.
Go tell them
to cripple limbs of Xu You'an
and then torture him brutally.
I want to repay the humiliation
I suffered a hundredfold.
What do you want?
I can give you everything.
I can take you
to find the kingfisher phoenix crown.
Consider it my sincerity.
But I want Xu You'an to leave alive.
Fine.
Then tidy up your clothes
and wipe the sweat
off your face and neck.
I want Xu You'an to see
how I treat my guests.
(Now I can only use cultural relics
to buy time)
(to protect Xu You'an and Chun'er.)
(The Xiaosheng Society
wants those two so badly.)
(They are probably more
than just cultural relics.)
(Whatever secret lies behind all this,)
(they mustn't get them.)
(Xu Fan must die.)
(And the Xiaosheng Society
must be destroyed.)
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪